videogamenews.com 2007-02-06

# Video Game News, Inc. > Home ( DNN 4.4.0 )

Video Game News, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Video Game News, Inc. Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Video Game News, Inc. website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

Video Game News, Inc. collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Video Game News, Inc. also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Video Game News, Inc.. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Video Game News, Inc. for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Video Game News, Inc. Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Video Game News, Inc. public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Video Game News, Inc. does not read any of your private online communications.

Video Game News, Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Video Game News, Inc. so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Video Game News, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Video Game News, Inc. and Video Game News, Inc. family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

Video Game News, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to operate the Video Game News, Inc. Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Video Game News, Inc. also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Video Game News, Inc. and its affiliates. Video Game News, Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Video Game News, Inc. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Video Game News, Inc. may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Video Game News, Inc. may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Video Game News, Inc., and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Video Game News, Inc. does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Video Game News, Inc. keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Video Game News, Inc., in order to determine what Video Game News, Inc. services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Video Game News, Inc. to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Video Game News, Inc. Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Video Game News, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Video Game News, Inc.; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Video Game News, Inc., or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Video Game News, Inc. Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Video Game News, Inc. pages, or register with Video Game News, Inc. site or services, a cookie helps Video Game News, Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Video Game News, Inc. Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Video Game News, Inc. features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Video Game News, Inc. services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

Video Game News, Inc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Video Game News, Inc. secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

Video Game News, Inc. will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Video Game News, Inc. encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Video Game News, Inc. is protecting your information.

Contact Information

Video Game News, Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Video Game News, Inc. has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Video Game News, Inc. at [admin@videogamenews.com](mailto:admin@videogamenews.com). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
